playposit.com 2019-07-16

# PlayPosit

**Last Updated:** May 24, 2018

**

## PRIVACY POLICY

**

### RIGHTS OF EUROPEAN DATA SUBJECTS UNDER THE GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR) 

If you are in one of the EU/EEA countries, beginning in May 25, 2018, you will be entitled to certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). 

First, you should know that PlayPosit, our presentation platform and related services (collectively, the “Service”) takes the minimal amount of information we need in order to offer our service. We do not sell or remarket information about our customers or users. 

By visiting the the Service or communicating with the Service you consent to the purposes for which we process your Personal Information. You will have a right to withdraw consent to processing. For the Personal Information we collect on the Service, this means you may withdraw your consent to processing by leaving the Service, suspending your account if you have registered, and requesting that we delete your Personal Information by contacting us at privacy@playposit.com. 

You will have the right to access your Personal Information that we hold. 

You will have a right to demand modification of inaccurate Personal Information. 

You will have the right to erasure of past data about you (your “right to be forgotten”). 

You will have the right to demand that we restrict processing of your Personal Information, under certain conditions, if you believe we have exceeded the legitimate basis for processing, processing is no longer necessary, are processing, or believe your Personal Information is inaccurate. 

You will have a right to data portability of Personal Information concerning you that you provided us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, subject to certain conditions. 

The Personal Information we collect on the Service is not used for automated decision making and profiling, except for our own customer communication via e-mail or support. And you can opt-out of direct marketing by the Service. 

The Service’s is a US based company with no physical presences in the EU. 

This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices for PlayPosit, our presentation platform and related services (collectively, the “Service”). Our Service allows users to organize and present knowledge. The Service provides Web-based tools to easily create interactive videos which consist of a collection of resources used to present to other users. We provide the Service from our Web site and from mobile applications, mobile sites or other internet points of presence that we may make available from time to time (collectively, our “Site”). By using or accessing our Service and Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By using the Services, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States. If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [help@playposit.com](mailto:help@playposit.com). 

**1\. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.** This Privacy Policy covers our collection and use of information when you use our Service and Site. It does not cover third party Web sites or applications to which we provide links from our Service.

**2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS.** In order to use the Service, users must submit their name and email to the Service. This is the only personally identifiable information we collect from users (including students). The Service provides users with one place to organize and present their knowledge and content. Students may sign up either by going to the site or by a teacher adding them to a class. We use the names and email address of students only to provide the Service, and do not disclose them to anyone other than a student’s own teachers or organization administrators except under the circumstances described in Section 5 below. 

**3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS.**

  * Personal Information You Provide at Registration. If you register for an account on our Service, we ask for your name and email address. 
  * Information We Collect When You Use Our Service. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Service. We keep track of your “clicks” and pages you view on our Site. We use “cookies” and obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, information about your browser software and operating system, and the date and time you access our site. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide certain features on our Site. The “Help” feature in most Web browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable some cookies altogether. Keep in mind that disabling cookies may result in some features of the Service not working properly. 

**4\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT.**

  * To Provide, Manage and Improve the Services. We use the personal information we collect from users to make the Service and its features available, and to improve and add features to the Service. We may also use this information to customize certain Service features for teachers. 
  * To Contact Users and Respond to Emails. We may also use contact information to provide teachers with announcements related to our services. If you email us, we may use your email addresses to respond. 

**5\. HOW WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION.** We do not share any personal information submitted to the Service by users with any third parties, except under the following limited circumstances: 

  * Third Party Service Providers. We rely on some third party service providers to assist us in operating the Service. For example, we may use third parties to host our Site or send messages. We provide personal information to these third party service providers in order to help us operates the Service, but we put in place contractual and/or technical protections that prohibit them from using that information, or it to any third party, except as necessary in operating the Service. 
  * Business Transfers. If we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, personal information you submit to the Service would likely be among the assets transferred to the acquirer. In the event of such an acquisition, the Privacy Policy in force at the time would continue to apply your information. 
  * To Protect Us and Others from Liability or Harm. We release message content and personal information if we believe we must do so to comply with the law, to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the safety and rights of us or our users. This does not include selling, renting, sharing or disclosing your information or content for commercial purposes. 
  * With Your Consent. We may also share your personal information or content with third parties if you give us your consent to do so. 

**7\. HOW TO VIEW AND EDIT YOUR INFORMATION; ACCOUNT DELETION**

  * Profile Information. You can view and modify your account information on the Service at any time.
  * Account Deletion. If you wish to delete your account or contact information from the Service, please email us at [help@playposit.com](mailto:help@playposit.com) requesting deletion. 

**8\. MESSAGE CONTENT.** We do not monitor, review or exercise any control over the resources used when using the Service (though we reserve the right to block resources that we reasonably believe may subject us or our users to liability). Accordingly, personal information included in the content of resources used on the Service is not governed by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to avoid including personally identifiable information about yourself or others in resources that will be shared or made public, and we encourage teachers to talk with their students about not including sensitive personal information in any resources used on the Service. 

**9\. SECURITY.** We take precautions to maintain the security and integrity of personal information you submit to the Service, including storage of your profile and personal information on a secure server behind a firewall. 

**10\. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.** We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If you maintain an account for the Service, we will notify you, at the email address you provide to us when you register for an account, of any material modifications to this Privacy Statement. 

**11\. HOW TO CONTACT US.** If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [help@playposit.com](mailto:help@playposit.com).
